Prophecy Time
Have you thrown this thing away?
No, sir.
You have to throw it away.
God loves you so much.
Thank you.
Deliverance Time
As wise man Christopher moves throughout the congregation he touches each and every one
of those in attendance.
The touch they are receiving is not just an ordinary touch, it is a touch of Jesus Christ, that will
dispel every shade of darkness in their lives.
As he is praying the prayer of faith, a women from the next row steps forward
and addresses wise man Christopher.
Moving closer and closer with every word, she clenches her hands in the fist and her stand is that of someone,
who is ready to fight.
She moves towards the wise man with every intention of fighting him.
Let us see what happens next in her encounter with wise man Christopher.
What do you want from me?
You small boy, you don’t have respect for old mothers like me.
Please, leave me alone.
I don’t want anything to disturb me.
Leave me alone.
OK?
Who are you?
You want to know who I am?
I am the queen of the world.
What do you mean by that?
Can't you see?
I am the queen of the world.
OK?
As a queen, how do you operate in this body?
I seduce people.
Both men and women.
Do you know what she is doing?
She is a mobile cashier.
I entered her through the internet when she opened her profile.
I saw a bright star in her and I entered her.
I gave her this ring and this mirror.
Where is the mirror?
Can't you find the mirror there?
There is a mirror which I use to monitor her all around.
What did you say?
She told me today that someone on the internet sent her to buy these things.
So, she bought them.
The person told her what and where to buy these things.
So, she went and bought them.
What do you say - what this is all about?
It is to seduce people.
I seduce great people.
People that are trying to make it, I bring them down.
Do you know what happened?
As a cashier, we gave her perfume we saw on the internet.
It is a body spray.
When she sprays it and you are her customer, you will smell it from a distance.
Then, you will remove whatever you have sold, whatever you have in your pocket and give her.
Immediately.
What are you saying, sir?
Even inside this bag, there is perfume.
Everywhere she is going – perfume.
Even if you take her inside a car, she will spray perfume.
She takes it everywhere.
Each time you spray this demonic perfume - what happens?
How do you use them?
I seduce more customers, as a giant queen of the world.
When you seduce these people - what happens to them?
I have many, many branches and she is the only one collecting money for us.
When she collects it, I bring it.
Once she has collected 1 000 Francs from you, we will collect million of dollars and pounds from you
and everything about you is finished; you will never make it in life.
She has captured many.
We have millions of dollars in our kingdom brought by her.
How does she capture these people?
Explain.
She captures them with the perfume.
Every time she goes out, she sprays.
They will say, "Oh, our girl has come. We were waiting for you. We just perceived the smell of your perfume."
Everybody will remove their money and give her.
But here she is; we collect everything from her.
And this mirror is to monitor her everywhere she is going.
How many of you are living in this body?
Five of us.
Mention your names one after the other.
Who is number one?
The queen.
Number two?
The idols.
Number three?
The lion.
Number four?
The snake.
Number five?
I will not say it.
Number five.
In the name of Jesus Christ - speak.
Number five?!
Anger.
How do you operate in this body?
Who do you mean, the queen or the idols?
The one who is allowed to talk.
How do you people operate in this body?
I, the idol, have destroyed the whole family.
No one can make it in that family.
This one wants to show me she can make it
but I told her she will not make it; she can't.
She will not make it in that family.
She cannot make it.
Many of them are running mental.
This one wants to show me she knows that Man.
Who is that Man to her?
What are you trying to do?
I am ready for the fight.
You are ready for what?
For the fight!
Why are you provoking me?
You were talking about some Man.
Who were you referring to?
Which Man are you talking about!?
That Man – you know Him; you know that Man.
Please, don’t look at me.
Your eyes...
You know, as I am a queen, you don’t have to look straight forward like that.
Your eyes are affecting me.
How does it affect you?
Too much fire.
As an idol, what have you done to members of the family of this lady?
I have rendered them useless; no one can give an account of anything.
Do you know why?
The father dedicated her to me.
When the mother gave birth to her, I saw the bright future in her head and I asked for her as a favour
from the father and he accepted.
That's why she has to come back to serve me.
She says she is a born-again.
Born to where?
She has to come back and give me a sacrifice.
What kind of a sacrifice?
As usual, she will give me goats and blood because I need blood to live.
What kind of blood do you need?
Animal blood, human blood – I need it to live.
I destroyed the son.
I gave her last son the spirit of sickle cell.
Each time that child fails, they will remove blood from this one,
this useless thing and give to him, which I don’t like.
They will do what?
They will remove her blood and give to him.
That's what I need from her so that she will come back and serve me.
Do you get it?
What have you done to this lady's marriage?
I have destroyed everything about that marriage.
The husband – I rendered him useless.
For three years, he has been doing nothing.
This useless thing thinks she can make it.
She will not make it.
How have you destroyed his job?
I have destroyed him.
Nobody gives him a contract.
When they promise to give him a contract, I will go there and stop the people.
When he goes there, they will jail him and say he is a fake man.
OK?
It is so that this one will suffer and come back to me but she said that she would not.
I have captured the rest of the members of the family but this one is stubborn.
She escaped from me.
I have rendered those people useless.
But this one is brighter and she told me she would not bow her knees before me.
But I said it before my idol kingdom that this girl will return.
Where is your kingdom?
My kingdom is in the father's house.
We have many people we have captured there.
Nine of them have been captured.
We rendered them mental.
Do you know the uncle is a principal?
We brought him back to nothing.
To my greatest surprise, I found myself here.
I am disgraced!
My kingdom will fall; I have many branches all over.
Right now, anything that has a beginning must have an end.
I plead with you.
Please, leave...
You have no option.
Leave her for me, please.
Your mission has come to an end.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come out of this body!
All over your body - Holy Ghost, fire!
Every part of your body!
Holy Ghost, fire - in the name of Jesus Christ!
Why are you doing this to me?
My company will fall.
Every part of your body!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Would you now leave me alone?
Right now, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ - go.
Do you want to fight?
Yes.
Are you ready?
Now, come.
I can't go there, it is too much fire.
I can't stand.
What did you say?
There is too much fire - I can't cross.
But you want to fight?
You people collected all our powers.
We cannot see or fight.
Thank You, Jesus.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come out of her!
Out!
You demon.
Out, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
In Jesus' name!
Amen.
Rise up.
You are delivered.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
How are you?
I'm fine.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
I am happy to see you, sir.
Rise up, stand up.
Have you set me out of the...
Am I free?
What do you mean?
You said you were...
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Do you remember what you have said?
No.
Jesus had delivered you.
Thank You, Jesus!
Follow Him.
Thank You, Jesus! Thank You, Lord!
OK. Let me just pick it one by one.
It talks about the perfume.
That does not mean that the perfume is bad.
OK?
Everything has old and new – the old nature and the new nature.
Everything.
Even your suit, there is a fake and a genuine one.
Are you with me?
Everything.
Satan is trying to copy.
Fake people are trying to copy.
Like I was telling you people about - the old nature demands to see because he lives by the senses.
There is a conflict between the old nature and the new nature.
There is what?
The old nature demands to see because he lives by the senses.
If you say you must see before you believe - this is a problem for you -
you will continue to be trapped by satan.
You will continue to be trapped by what?
Tell your neighbour, "If you say you must see before you believe, you are trapped."
Yes.
We do not see first, then believe.
We believe first, then see.
I have given you the message today, which is going to work for you.
Because you want to see, what you can see with your eyes.
This contradicts our natural way of thinking.
The world at large says 'seeing is believing'
- and they will show you how things work -
'seeing is believing'. But the Bible reverses the order - we must believe, then see.
So the perfume it talks about...
It does not mean that all the perfume...
In everything there are positive and negative.
There are the old nature and the new nature.
Let's listen to her.
Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
People of God, Emmanuel!
[God with us.]
My name is Ngwenye Prudentia, I am coming from Cameroon.
The man beside me is my lovely husband.
The man beside him is my brother and my son.
I'm here to testify to the goodness of God, for what Lord has used Prophet T.B. Joshua to do in my life.
I was having nightmares.
It all started when I wanted to do an American visa lottery for my daughter which I went to the internet for
and I asked my nephew to open a Facebook account for me.
He did it.
We played the lottery.
After that, I opened my Facebook profile and I saw somebody requested to be my friend.
I accepted him as my friend.
Anytime I would go to the internet, he was always online.
When I asked him where he was from, he said he was from America.
I told him that I had some problems and I wanted him to help me.
He asked me what type of problem.
I said financial problems.
He said OK, he would do that.
He said he would send something to me.
When I went to my Facebook profile the next day, I saw an amount of money.
I asked him if he was the one who sent me the money.
He said yes.
I asked him how I was going to collect this money.
And you didn’t know him?
Yes, sir.
He said he was sent to indicate to me how to collect the money.
When I got there the next day, I saw a file with certain articles
and a note indicating where I could buy those articles, which I did.
I went directly to the store in Cameroon and bought those articles.
After buying the articles, I went back to Facebook.
I told him that I had bought those things.
He said I should send him my account number so that he could deposit the money into my account.
I asked if I could ask him a question and he said yes.
I told him that it was good that he wanted to help me but I would want to know his name and see his picture.
He said, the next morning he would do everything possible to send his picture.
The next day, I went to check for his name and his picture, with my daughter.
My daughter opened the file.
People of God, I saw something I had never seen in my life.
I was shocked – I even fainted there.
This is what I saw in my Facebook profile – this picture with no name.
I was shocked.
I didn’t know how to explain it and nobody knew about me.
You have never discussed this with anyone?
No.
What about your husband standing there?
He doesn’t know anything about it.
Yey!
Rise up.
The husband says that he sees it for the first time.
The husband is on the floor.
I'm finished.
You are finished?
Man of God, I'm finished!
I stay in the same house with her but I've never seen this before.
Man of God, help me! I'm finished!
You see it for the first time?
Yes, I'm finished!
This is my first time seeing this, man of God.
Even the ring that she was showing – I have never seen it before.
You have never seen the ring before?
The ring. Yes.
You see the ring for the first time?
Yes, man of God.
Let me ask the wife.
Madam, did they ask you not to tell anyone?
Yes, sir. They said it was a covenant and I should not tell anybody.
He said I made a covenant with him and I have to work for him.
Let's see the picture again.
After you saw this picture and the ring, what started to happen to you?
When I saw this picture, he came to me in my dream that very night
and told me that I had made a covenant with him, I belonged to his kingdom and would work for him.
He said those articles I bought were for seduction - both men and women.
The man came to you in the dream?
Yes, sir.
How does he look like?
He's a very giant, tall man.
And you have never seen him physically before?
No, sir.
Look, we are addressing the whole world now.
People don't know this kind of things happens.
From which country is the person who sent you the picture?
He said he was from America.
I just saw this picture but no name.
The day you received the picture - he came to you in the dream.
Yes, sir.
Tell us what he told you when he came to you in the dream.
He came to me in my dream and said I belonged to him, I had made a covenant with him and would work
in his kingdom.
He told me the articles he gave me were for seducing men and women.
Immediately, I started hearing a certain voice talking to me.
What were the voices telling you?
The voice said that before I would go to my job, I must use this spray.
Since then, I had never done anything without the spray.
I could not do without this spray – I would buy it in the packet.
Every morning before I went to my job, I would spray this perfume.
What happened when you sprayed it?
My customers would already know that I was coming.
When I asked how they knew I was coming they said they could smell my perfume.
I'm a "daily collector".
What these things you used for?
The ring is used for seducing great men and women.
And you succeeded in seducing of many great men?
Yes, thousands of them.
When you seduced them, they would go out with you?
Some of them would go out with me and immediately they did that,
they were finished and would never give account of anything in life.
She is free now.
The battle is for Jesus.
God is using me to fight the whole world that is negative.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Do you know that this picture is a symbol of "trillions" of people all over the world who worship these things?
Trillion of people are under the influence of this thing.
It is like we are fighting trillion people all over the world.
They have devoured thousand people.
All they are interested in is to bring you down and turn you to slaves or dogs.
The husband did not know what was happening in the house.
Aren't you surprised about that ring?
You said that many heroes and great men you had got and brought down?
Yes, sir.
When I sprayed this perfume, before I would get to you, you would already know that I was coming.
When I got there, the customers would tell me the they knew I was coming.
When I asked how they knew, they would say they could smell my spray and wanted to know the name
and where to get it.
I gave some of them the name and directed them where to get it.
The next day, when that man came to carry me to that kingdom, I would see some of those people there.
Anyone that used this spray would be initiated.
We all need deliverance.
Look at the husband.
He is surprised.
Don't worry.
Madam, it is all right.
Stand up.
Man of God - help me.
People of God, help me to say thank you to the man of God.
This woman has destroyed me.
Any contract I touch – nothing can progress.
Making love with her is a problem.
When I make love with her – if I have an appointment tomorrow, it vanishes.
Everything is finished, right down to the house.
Nothing is finished. It is all right.
I want to join your family.
Help me to beg my husband, that he would forgive me.
No, don't worry. I'm going to see two of you.
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 05/01/2019